

Due to graduate in 2016, I have acquired technical knowledge and skills from my course as well as practical and business skills from my industrial year in a software company in the Netherlands. I have used a range of languages, operating systems and development tools as well as experiencing the system development life cycle. Specialising in mobile technology.

## PERSONAL DETAILS

Name Amelia Davis

Address 14 Tottenham Court Road, London, W1T 1JY

Phone number +44 20 7946 0638

Email address amelia.davis@mail.uk

Driving license B, AM, A

## WORK EXPERIENCE

2015 - present Junior software developer

Explore the web ltd, London

Used a range of languages, operating systems and development tools as well as experiencing the system development life cycle. Specialising in mobile technology, I am keen to develop as a graduate trainee in software development.

2007 - 2010 Website analyst

Quality ltd, London

· Creating online analyses

- · Writting personal branding plans
- Online marketingplan opstellen voor de diverse titels
- · Content marketing en content management

2007 - 2010 Online marketing

Advertisy, Manchester

- · Analyse and optimize positions within different search engines
- Search engine optimalisation
- Leading large linkbuilding activities
- · On-site SEO research and writing optimalisation rapports

## **EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS**

2012 - 2014 Computer Science and Software Engineering

University of London

BSc Computer Science and So4ware Engineering with industrial year. Predicted 2:1, Modules include object oriented programming, mobile applications, AI and systems development.

2012 - 2014 BTEC Level 3 ICT and A-level maths

Highbridge College